

## SYAHIRAH SAID ADMINISTRATION

+971-524149878



irabajerai@gmail.com



**Abu Dhabi - United Arab Emirates** 

# PROFILE SUMMARY

Administration skills with 3+ years of experience handling confidential paper and digital work and making routine office tasks as efficient as possible. Proven managerial experience supervising clerks and routine office duties. Strong multitasking, organizational, customer service and Data Entry Skills. Aiming to leverage my qualifications to fill an managerial role at the organization.

## **SKILLS**

- Proficient in Microsoft Suit like
- MicroSoft Word
- MicroSoft Access
- MicroSoft Excel
- Microsoft PowerPoint.
- Management Skills
- Proficiant in Computer Operations.
- Leadership & Teamwork Skills
- Communication and Presentation Skills
- Attention to detail | Technology.
- Problem Solving Skills
- Time Management skills
- Data Entry with 45+ word per minute.
- Ability to meet deadlines | IT Skills
- Interpersonal communication
- Strong background supporting Windows and OS.
- Experience with email administration.
- Manage the hardware, software and user support.
- Knowledge of IP telephony
- Adaptibility & Flexibility Skills
- Emotional Quotient EQ Skills
- Creativity | Editing | Digital Production
- Documentation
- Emotional Quotient EQ Skills

## **ABOUT ME**

Nationality: Malaysia

Passport No:

Date Of Birth: 03/04/1995 Marital Status: Married **Tourist Visa** Visa Type:

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bachelor Of Business Administration in Management and** Entrepreneurship.

University Kuala Lumpur - Malaysia 2016 - 2018

Graduated with 2.83 CGPA

STPM at SMK Dato Bentara Luar 2013-2014

Graduated with 2.67 CGPA

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM) at SMK Sung Siew 2008-2012 Graduated with 1A 3B+ 1B 2D

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Administration Officer**

2020 - 2021

## Reliva Company

- Deliver executive support to the Director of Engineering and 190+ people in the department.
- Offer travel support, calendar assistance and organization, maintain vacation and attendance records.
- Support human resources with all new hire candidate needs.
- Monitor building maintenance and expansion, schedule conference rooms, annual event coordination and implementation, and serve as backup support to other departments.

#### **Admin and Management Officer** 2019 - 2020

Falcon Universal Sdn Bhd

- Filled the data entry for students to study abroad.
- Handled enquiries and requests
- Assisted in handling maintenance of office equipments
- Submit documents or take any documets to place requested
- Receive or prepare courier service.
- Perform other tasks assigned by superior
- Simplified data retrieval processes, department record, maintenance.
- Typing and Compiling of reports, saving company an average of 200+ hours.

#### **Human Resources Interenship** 2018 - 2019 **Tradewinds Plantation Berhad**

- Assisted in Human Resources department in Administration, Recruitment and Compensation & Benefts
- Did data entry for documentation.
- Filled the HR Project Data and document management
- Assisted the Payrol manager in data entry.
- Assisted the Recuitment manager in handling new intake staff

## **DECLARATION**

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above mentioned particular.